Sam, what's up, man? Hey, how's it
going? Hey, how you feel about being a
panther, man? Oh, man, I'm That's
awesome. That sounds awesome. Who you
with?
I'm with my family right now. Awesome,
man. Congrats, man. We're excited to
have you.
>> [applause]
>> I'm going to hand you off to our to our
owner, David Tepper, okay? All righty.
All right, man. Congrats.
Thank you.
Hey, hey, Sam, where you at right now?
I'm back at home with my family right
now. Which home?
Uh Shawnee, Kansas.
Shawnee, Kansas? Kansas City area. All
right. All right, cool. Cool. You good?
I'm Yes, I'm happy. I'm excited.
Happy, [laughter] great, great. Sam, I'm
going to hand you off to the coach right
here, okay? All righty. All right, I'll
see you later.
See you.
What's up, Sam?
Hey, how's it going?
>> I hope you like running the ball.
Oh, I love it. Okay, that's that's what
we do, okay? I'm going to pass you over
here. This is coach Goodwin. He's going
to be coaching you up here. All righty.
Sam, I'm excited. You ready to go?
Yes, sir, coach. I'm ready. Well, make
sure you get your ass in shape, eat
another peanut butter and jelly
sandwich, and let's go get do this
thing. Yes, sir. I will. I will.
We're good.
>> [applause]
>> Can't wait to get you here, bro.
Hey, uh
I'll give you a call back in a few
minutes.
Okay, sounds great. All right, man.
>> [music]
[music]